http://www.overrunz.com/privacy.php

Follow @overrunz
Your Price: $0.00Save Over 0%MORE INFOYour Price: $0.00Save Over 0%MORE INFOYour Price: $0.00Save Over 0%MORE INFOYour Price: $0.00Save Over 0%MORE INFO
Privacy Policy
Introduction
We at Overrunz International Inc. are committed to
respecting your online privacy and recognize your need
for appropriate protection and management of any personally
identifiable information ("Personal Information")
you share with us.
Overrunz has established this Online Privacy Policy
so that you can understand the care with which we intend
to treat and respect your Personal Information.
Personal Information means any information that may
be used to identify an individual, including, but not
limited to, a first and last name, a home or other
physical address and an email address or other contact
information, whether at work or at home. In general,
you can visit the Overrunz web pages without telling
us who you are or revealing any Personal Information
about yourself.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information
on the Web, we may transfer that Information within
Overrunz or to Overrunz' third-party service providers,
across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction
to other countries or jurisdictions around the world
for the sole purpose of having you order processed
effectively, safely, and under strict security.
is collected, transferred, or retained.
or not to accept them and how to remove them.
parts of the Web site.
site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information
that does not contain Personal Information for trends
and statistics.
To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following
principles:
legally required.
involve our interaction with you.
If you chose to have a relationship with Overrunz,
such as a contractual or other business relationship
or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact
you in connection with that business relationship.
disclosure.
and corrections about your Personal Information to:
info@overrunz.com and we will make reasonable efforts
to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information
that we hold as soon as practicable.
to help us deliver products, information, and services.
Service providers are also an important means by which
Overrunz maintains its Web site and mailing lists.
Overrunz will take reasonable steps to ensure that
these third-party service providers are obligated to
protect Personal Information on Overrunz' behalf.
without consent.
Back to Top
Children's
Privacy
Overrunz.com is not structured to attract children.
Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information
from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.
Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.
If you have any comments or questions regarding our
Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@overrunz.com.
While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will
address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon
as possible.
web site for a reasonable period of time.
Twitter (@overrunz)
